let questions = [
    {
        question: 'In the precolonial Brazil, the area that is now Sao Paulo was occupied by various native tribes headed by a cacique. What is the name of the cacique of the Tupiniquim tribe who converted to Christianity in the mid 16th century?',
        answer: 'Tibiriçá',
        options: [
            'Malloquete',
            'Tamanaco',
            'Chacao',
            'Tibiriçá',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the oldest museum in the city, founded in December 24, 1905?',
        answer: 'Pinacoteca de São Paulo',
        options: [
            'Museu de Arte de São Paulo Assis Chateaubriand',
            'Pinacoteca de São Paulo',
            'Museu de Arte Sacra de São Paulo',
            'Museu do Ipiranga',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'The construction of which building, that still stands today, marked the official founding of Sao Paulo?',
        answer: 'Patio do Colegio',
        options: [
            'Edificio Copan',
            'Patio do Colegio',
            'Teatro São Pedro',
            'Templo de Salomão',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'Meaning flag bearers, bandeirantes came to Sao Paulo in the late 17th century for what reason?',
        answer: 'To find gold',
        options: [
            'To search for oil',
            'To find gold',
            'To fight in a war against Spain',
            'To form a new nation',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'What now stands on the location in Sao Paulo where Brazilian independence announced by Emperor Dom Pedro I of Brazil on September 7, 1822?',
        answer: 'Monumento do Ipiranga',
        options: [
            'Monumento do Ipiranga',
            'Marco Zero',
            'Theatro Municipal',
            'Jardim da Luz',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'After Brazilian independence, what was the main cash crop in Sao Paulo?',
        answer: 'Coffee',
        options: [
            'Cotton',
            'Rubber',
            'Bananas',
            'Coffee',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the the most popular football team in São Paulo?',
        answer: 'Corinthians',
        options: [
            'São Paulo',
            'Corinthians',
            'Palmeiras',
            'Juventus',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'Approximately how many pizzas are sold each day in São Paulo?',
        answer: '572.000',
        options: [
            '425.000',
            '683.000',
            '572.000',
            '384.000',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'Approximately how many people live in São Paulo today(2021)?',
        answer: '12.325.232',
        options: [
            '15.728.356',
            '13.138.921',
            '12.325.232',
            '14.756.013',
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'When was founded the Municipal Theater of São Paulo?',
        answer: '1911',
        options: [
            '1915',
            '1911',
            '1917',
            '1921',
        ]
    },
];